Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Insecticide plots. Plot I4 right, I3 left. 119 DDT. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-02 (Box 6, Item 52.059)
    - Animal Husbandry. Bulletin 543. Figures for Bulletin. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1952-09 (Box 6, Item 52.060)
    - Rabbit. Spontaneous spinal fracture. Low P ration. Heinemann. Internal organs. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-05-29 (Box 6, Item 52.061)
    - Rabbit. Spontaneous spinal fracture. Low P ration. Heinemann. Internal organs. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.062)
    - Rabbit - X-Ray negatives. Heinemann. 2 4x5 x-ray negatives; no prints. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.063)
    - Animal Husbandry. Figures for Bulletin. 3 5x7 negs. No prints. 1952-09 (Box 6, Item 52.064)
    - Steer work. 4 prints from 52.064 negatives. No negatives. 1952-09 (Box 6, Item 52.065)
    - The effect of dipping clusters in different concentrations of 2,4-D acid. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-07 (Box 6, Item 52.066)
    - Seasonal Rise in Infestations, 1949-1952. Adult maggot emergence. Frick. 11 negatives: 5 5x7, 6 4x5. No prints. Cherry fruit fly. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.067)
    - Daily Cherry Fruit Fly Emergence from the Soil: 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952. Frick. 5 5x7 negs. No prints. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.068)
    - Daily Bait Trap Catches: 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952. Cherry Friut Fly. Frick. 6 5x7 negatives. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.069)
    - Cylinder Type Bait Traps. Frick. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.077)
    - Crew Pictures Harvesting and Weighing. 10-6 and 12-53. Left to right: Dee Smith, Ester Lynch, Dolly Huard, Fred Randall, John Chiara, Al Barker. People identifications should be right to left?. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP249, WSUP250. 1953-06 (Box 6, Item 53.001)
    - Sioux Tomato. 100ug 2,4-D acid. 4x5 neg. No print. 1953-01-17 (Box 6, Item 53.002)
    - Sioux Tomato. 1 ug 2,4-D acid. 4x5 neg. No print. 1953-01-17 (Box 6, Item 53.003)
    - Grape Variety Bronx. Vineyard B2. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1953-10-23 (Box 6, Item 53.004)
    - Church #5 Rootstock Studies. Permanent vine compared to Concord on Mourvediex reposition (?). 4 4x5 negs. Prints. 1953-10-06 (Box 6, Item 53.005)
    - Technique used in applying 2,4-D. 3mm platinum wire loop. Clore. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP251. 1953-08 (Box 6, Item 53.006)
    - Station Concord Vineyard A36. 6' trellis spacing 9X8'. Cover crop barley and Hairy vetch. Drilled 8-7-52. 4x5 neg.; print. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.007)
    - Grape Nutritional Troubles Unknown. Concord vineyard A36. 4 4x5 negs.; prints. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.008)
    - Late 2,4-D symptoms. Church Vineyard #5. Taken on soil between rows. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP252. 1953-10-12 (Box 6, Item 53.009)
    - Grape Vineyard, Church #5. Height of Trellis Studies. Rows 252 and 253 compared. 5 4x5 negs.; prints. 1953-10-12 (Box 6, Item 53.010)
    - Insecticide Studies. Roza 20,21,22. looking south between plots 5 iii and 10 iii. Also looking N. 4x5 neg.; print. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.011)
    - Insecticide in soil studies. Border effect of 238# DDT/acre. 10-8-53. Plots 5 III and 10 III Looking S. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP253. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.012)
    - Insecticide in the soil studies. Plots 5 III and 10 III. Laterial (sic) movement of 238# DDT. similar to 53.012. 4x5 neg.; print. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.013)
    - Insecticide studies. Roza 20,21,22. 4 I and 3 I from front to back. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.014)
    - Insecticide Studies. Roza E 20, 21, 22. Carryover plot border between 5 III and 12 III approx. 5'. 4x5 neg. No print. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.015)
    - Insecticide Studies. Roza E 20, 21, 22. 4 III and 2 III. 4 more dwarfing than 2. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1953-10-08 (Box 6, Item 53.016)
    - Insecticide in soil studies. 238# DDT on left. 9.5# DDT on right. Double exposure?. 4x5 neg.; print. 1953-07-08 (Box 6, Item 53.017)
    - Aerial Views of Insecticide plots. Roza E20, 21, 22. Taken around 500' alt. 4 4x5 negs. Prints. 1953-10-14 (Box 6, Item 53.018)
    - 2,4-D symptoms on grapes from Kennewick. Used to evaluate injury on survey of contaminated area. Light red - severe injury. Blue - Moderate injury. Yellow - Symptoms present and detectable. Green - occaisional affected lead but no damage. Clore. 5 5x7 neg (Box 6, Item 53.019)
    - Grape rootstocks from Field B-2. Set out in 1945. 5 5x7 negs.; prints. 1953-06 (Box 6, Item 53.020)
    - Harry Palmer with John Deere grape cultivation attachment. 2 5x7 negs. Prints. WSUP254. 1953-04-30 (Box 6, Item 53.021)
    - Tool arrangement on John Deere for grape cultivation. 2 5x7 negs. Prints. 1953-04-30 (Box 6, Item 53.022)
    - Sioux Tomato. 100ug 2,4-D acid. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1953-01-17 (Box 6, Item 53.023)
    - Church Vineyard #4, Kennewick. Concord grapes showing earlier 2,4-D symptoms with resulting recovery. 2 5x7 negs. Prints. 1953-09-03 (Box 6, Item 53.024)
    - Grapes, Cotton, Blackeyed peas, tomatoes susceptibility to 2,4-D acid. 4 5x7 negs.; prints. 1953-08-27 (Box 6, Item 53.025)
    - Field bean trials. 4 5x7 negs.; prints. 1953-08-04 (Box 6, Item 53.026)
    - Tomato Curly-top ploots interplanted with susceptible sugar beets adjacent to 1 acre of resistant beets. L. to R. John Chiara and Fred Randall. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP255. 1953-08-04 (Box 6, Item 53.027)
    - Grape varieties. (10-12-53 and 10-23-53). Clusters of Interlaken seedless, Black Monukka, Cardinal,. 5 5x7 negs.; prints. WSUP256. 1953-10-12 (Box 6, Item 53.028)
    - A. Mn deficiency (possible). B. 2,4-D. C. Zn deficiency. D. Healthy. 3 5x7 negs. No prints. 1953-10-23 (Box 6, Item 53.029)
    - Maps of Dispersion of Cherry Fruit Fly Adults from I.E.S. orchard. 1950, 1951, 1953. 3 5x7 negs. No prints. 1953 (Box 6, Item 53.030)
    - Ewes on Ladino Clover pasture, old baseball field below Adm. Bldg. 4x5 neg. No print. 1953 (Box 6, Item 53.031)
    - South Moses Lake. Onions. Zinc deficient and normal- 1953. Boawn. No negative. Note inside envelope: negative loaned to Viets, Ft. Collins 1/13/58. 1953 (Box 6, Item 53.032)
    - Quincy. Corn. Zinc deficient corn plants. Boawn. No negative. Note inside envelope: negative loaned to Viets, Ft. Collins 1/13/58. 1953 (Box 6, Item 53.033)
    - Roza Unit. Bean. Zinc deficient Red Mexican bean plants - 1953. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1953 (Box 6, Item 53.034)
    - Coal Storage. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP257. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.001)
    - Herdsmans house, lower unit. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP258. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.002)
    - Irrigators house, lower unit. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP259. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.003)
    - Apts. lower Unit. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP260. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.004)
    - Packing Shed, Roza. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP261. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.006)
    - Garage Roza. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP262. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.007)
    - Pruitt Trailer. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP263. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.008)
    - Irrigator house Roza. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP264. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.009)
    - Farm Managers house Roza. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP265. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.010)
    - New Shop Bldg. Building under construction. 4 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP266, WSUP267. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.011)
    - Herdsmans Trailer. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP268. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.012)
    - Herdsmans Trailer. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.013)
    - Storage Shed West of West Bldg. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP269. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.014)
    - Trailer at Roza shop. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP270. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.015)
    - Trailer at Packing Shed Roza. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP271. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.016)
    - Curly top virus bean studies. D-6, IES. Bill Zaumeyer, Bliss Dana, Winton Wilson. Curly top bean plots. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP272. 1954-08-06 (Box 6, Item 54.017)
    - Roza, steer pastures. Ladino - OG 7A. Heinemann, Van Keunen. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP273. 1954-08 (Box 6, Item 54.018)
    - Variety Orchard, Fogle. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.020)
    - Alberta Block, Proebsting. 9 4x5 negatives; no prints. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.021)
    - Crown gall on sugar beet from Roza. 4x5 neg.; print. 1954-11 (Box 6, Item 54.023)
    - 1954 Beans, Expt. 72P C-6,7,8, Roza. 4 spacings at first bloom 7 weeks after planting. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1954 (Box 6, Item 54.024)
    - Orchardgrass - Ladino Pasture. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.026)
    - Orchardgrass Pasture. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.027)
    - Tall fescue pasture. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.028)
    - Tall fescue - Alfalfa pasture. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.029)
    - Tall fescue- Ladino pasture. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.030)
    - Orchardgrass - Alfalfa Pasture. Odemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.031)
    - Beef Pasture (Roza). SE from concrete water box. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.032)
    - Beef Pastures (Roza). SW from well house. Oldemeyer. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.033)
    - Beef Pasture (Roza). E. from W end of alley. Oldemeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.034)
    - Beef Pasture (Roza). (E. from W end of alley - crossed out) .Oldemeyer. Smoke in background. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP274. 1954-05-05 (Box 6, Item 54.035)
    - Beef Pasture Exp. (Roza). RW. Van Keuren. 3 4x5 negatives, one with a person in back. No prints. 1954-10-04 (Box 6, Item 54.036)
    - Branding Calves and Calves in Winter - feedlot. R.W. Van Keuren. None seem to show branding. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1954-12-08 (Box 6, Item 54.038)
    - About August 7, 1954. Heinemann. 4x5 neg. No print. 1954-08-07 (Box 6, Item 54.039)
    - IES office Bldg. and grounds. 9 4x5 negs. No prints. No number on envelope. WSUP275-WSUP279. 1955-10-20 (Box 6, Item 55.000)
    - Sheep Pasture Exp. (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 7 4x5 negatives, one with a man. No prints. 1955 (Box 6, Item 55.001)
    - Sheep Pasture Exp. (Roza). Show perference for Ladino clover in pasture mixture. RW Van Keuren. 4x5 neg. No print. 1955 (Box 6, Item 55.002)
    - Beef Pasture Exp. (Roza). RW. Van Keuren. 15 4x5 negatives; no prints. 1955 (Box 6, Item 55.003)
    - Corn Variety trial (Roza). RW Van Keuren. Neg. from 35mm slides. 2 4x5 negs, one with 2 men weighing corn. No print. WSUP280. 1955 (Box 6, Item 55.004)
    - Clipping Beef Pasture Plots with Rotary Mower (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP281. 1955-03-02 (Box 6, Item 55.005)
    - Airport Ranch, Sunnyside. Zinc deficient corn on old sugar beet ground. Normal corn on old alfalfa ground in background. - 1955. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1955 (Box 6, Item 55.006)
    - Alfalfa - Cheatgrass. Oldemeyer. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.002)
    - Alfalfa Variety trials (1) D33-34. (2) B-3. RW Van Keuren. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1956-07 (Box 6, Item 56.003)
    - Cereal Variety Plots. RW Van Keuren. 9 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP282. 1956-07-17 (Box 6, Item 56.005)
    - Corn Exp. Plots (Roza). RW. Van Keuren. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1956-07 (Box 6, Item 56.006)
    - Hops. RW Van Keuren. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP283. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.007)
    - Hybrid Mint (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.008)
    - Orchardgrass Variety Exp. RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.009)
    - Blk 45, Columbia Basin Potato. "Fern Leaf" condition of potato on right. At left normal growth resulting from sidedressing with ZnSO4 - 1956. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.010)
    - Copy from Slide. Skunk Damage to Alkali Bee Site, Peach Orchard. Sept. 1956. 4x5 neg.; print. 1956-09 (Box 6, Item 56.100)
    - Copies from Color Slides. Skunk Damage to Alkali Bee sites. 1956 and 1958. No negatives. One print dated 7/30/58, another Sept. 1956. Other two undated but labeled Copy, skunk Damage. 1958-07-30 (Box 6, Item 56.101)
    - Copies from Color Slides. Skunk Damage to Alkali Bee sites. 1956 and 1958. No negatives. 4 prints. One print dated Sept. 1956. 1959-09 (Box 6, Item 56.101)
    - Copy form Slide. Entrance to Alkali Bee Nest. 1956. 4x5 neg.; print. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.102)
    - Copy from Slide. 1956. Alkali Bee and Nest Entrance. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.103)
    - Copies from color Slides. Alkali Bee, Nest and Nesting Area. 1956-58. No negatives. One print dated 1956 is the same as 56.101. The other is dated 8/14/58. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.104)
    - Aerial Photos, I.E.S. 1956. By ECK. ECK is probably Ed Klostermeyer. 5 4x5 negs.; prints. WSUP300. 1956 (Box 6, Item 56.105)
    - Corn variety trials - Roza Unit. C. Zimmerman shown examining corn. Photo taken by H. Potter. R. Van Keuren. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP284. 1957-10-30 (Box 6, Item 57.001)
    - Constant Temp. Cabinets. Dick Cressman. 4x5 neg. No print. 1957-12-20 (Box 6, Item 57.003)
    - Corn. Exp. Wash-P-103. Shows phosphate response on corn. Foreground - no P2O5. Bachground - 400 P2O5 Broadcast. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1957 (Box 6, Item 57.004)
    - Bean. Exp. Wash-P-103. Shows phosphate respnse on Red Mexican beans. Boawn. 3 4x5 negs. Prints. 1957 (Box 6, Item 57.005)
    - Hops. Zinc deficient sidearm of hops. Boawn. Print; no negative. Note inside envelope: negative loaned to Viets, Ft. Collins 1/13/58. 1957 (Box 6, Item 57.006)
    - Rye cover trials (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 1958-03-27 (Box 6, Item 58.001)
    - Rye cover trials (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP285. 1958-04-18 (Box 6, Item 58.002)
    - Rye cover trials (Roza). RW Van Keuren. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP286. 1958-04-18 (Box 6, Item 58.002b)
    - 2. Stephenson #II. Old stack site W. Wapato Wn. Alkali Bee sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.002c)
    - Sheep Pastures (Jean Dawson prop). RW Van Keuren. 4 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP287. 1958-05 (Box 6, Item 58.003)
    - 3 and 4. Stephenson East Site. Alkali bee sites. W. Wapato, Wn. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.003b)
    - Ad. Bldg. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1958-05 (Box 6, Item 58.004)
    - Frenchman Wasteway Plots. Also aerial views. RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 1958-07 (Box 6, Item 58.005)
    - 5. Ray Martin. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.005b)
    - Grass Seed trials F19-18. RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negatives, one with a man. No prints. 1958-07 (Box 6, Item 58.006)
    - 6, 7-8. Trudeau. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.006b)
    - Wahluke Wasteway Site. RW Van Keuren. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP288. 1958-10 (Box 6, Item 58.007)
    - Frenchman Wasteway Site. RW Van Keuren. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 1958-10 (Box 6, Item 58.008)
    - Beef Sudan Pastures. RW Van Keuren. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1958 (Box 6, Item 58.009)
    - 9 and 9a. Don Stephenson Artificial. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.009a)
    - 9. Don Stephenson Artificial. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.009b)
    - 11. Gaugh. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.011b)
    - 12. Stephenson # IV. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.012b)
    - 13. Stephenson #V, W. Side of farm. Alkali Bee Site. W. Wapato, Wn. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.013b)
    - 16. F. A. Ray. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.016b)
    - 17. Winters. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.017b)
    - 18. Heilman. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.018)
    - 19. Benson Bee site. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Site. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.019)
    - 20-25. South Satus Bee Sites. No negatives. Prints 20 - 25. 8/13 and 8/14/58. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.020a)
    - 20. Newquist. Satus, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.020b)
    - 21. Mormon Derrick. Satus. Wn. Area. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.021b)
    - 22. Locust Grove Site. Satus, Wn. Area. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.022b)
    - 23. Diversion Site. Satus, Wn. Area. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.023b)
    - 24. Pumphouse Site. Satus Area, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.024b)
    - 24. Pumphouse Site. Satus Area, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/13/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-13 (Box 6, Item 58.024c)
    - 25. Shelton. Satus, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.025b)
    - 26-40. N. of Grandview and sunnyside. 1958. No negatives. Prints from 26 to 40 except 36. All 8.11/58. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.026b)
    - 26. Smasne. N. Grandview, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.026c)
    - 27. Cook Artificial Site. N. Grandview, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.027b)
    - 28. Rademacher. N. Grandview, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.028b)
    - 29. Rademacher Dry. N. Grandview, Wash. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.029b)
    - 30. Rademacher. N. Grandview, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.030b)
    - 31. Kendall. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.031b)
    - 32. T. Cook, Simmons. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.032b)
    - 33. Bob Wright. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.033b)
    - 34. Bob Wright. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. Chevrolet pickup truck. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.034b)
    - 35. Callison Farms. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.035b)
    - 36. Chaffee. N/ Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.036b)
    - 37. MacIntire. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.037b)
    - 38. Hulbart. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.038b)
    - 39. Sandlin. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.039b)
    - 40. Sandlin West. N. Sunnyside, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/11/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-11 (Box 6, Item 58.040b)
    - Photos of Columbia Basin Bee Sites. 7/29/58. No negatives. Prints of Nos. 51 - 61 except 54. 7/29, 7/30, and 7/31/58. 1958-07-29 (Box 6, Item 58.051b)
    - 51. Bee Sites. Red Krete, Quincy area. 7/29/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-29 (Box 6, Item 58.051c)
    - 52. Bee Site NE of Quincy, Wn. Oren Emerson. 7/29/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-29 (Box 6, Item 58.052b)
    - 53. Bee Sites. Jay Peterson. N.E. of Quincy. 7/29/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-29 (Box 6, Item 58.053b)
    - 55. Bee Site, Soap Lake area. Brockhaug. 7/30/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-30 (Box 6, Item 58.055b)
    - 56. Bee Site. L.E. Hall. N. Soap Lake. 7/30/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-30 (Box 6, Item 58.056b)
    - 57. Bee Sites. L. E. Hall. Soap Lake area. 7/30/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-30 (Box 6, Item 58.057b)
    - 58. Bee Sites. Norman Vehrs, Moses Lake area. 7/30/58. H. Weaver, Gus Hokason, Co. agent and Field man for Dickinson Seed Co. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP301. 1958-07-30 (Box 6, Item 58.058b)
    - 59. Bee Sites. Hand. Moses Lake area. 7/31/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-31 (Box 6, Item 58.059b)
    - 60. A Bee Site. G. Locke, Othello area. 7/31/58. H. Weaver and Co. Agent C. Voss. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP302. 1958-07-31 (Box 6, Item 58.060b)
    - 61. Dw Farm (Oberding?). Othello, Wn area. Alkali Bee Site. 7/231/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-07-31 (Box 6, Item 58.061b)
    - 1-19, 63 and 108. West Wapato area Bee Sites. No negatives. Prints of Nos. 2, 3 and 4, 5, (6, 7, 8), 9 and 9a, 9 and 9a, 11, 12, 17, 18, 63, 108, 108, 108. 1958 (Box 6, Item 58.063)
    - 63. Van der Graffe. W. Wapato, Wn. Alkali Bee Sites. 8/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-08-14 (Box 6, Item 58.063b)
    - 70. Byrnes west End. Gardena, Wash Alkali Bee Sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.070)
    - 105 and 107. 70-89- 1958. Gardena, Wn. Bee Sites. No negatives. Prints of Nos. 70,73, 74, 75 and 76,81, 85, 88, 89, 105. 1958 (Box 6, Item 58.070a)
    - 73. Byrnes Parking Site. Gardena wash. Alkali Bee Sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.073)
    - Van Nortwick House Site. Alkali Bee Sites, Gardena Wn. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.074)
    - 75 and 76. Alkali Bee Sites. Gardena, Wn. Van Nortwick Field Site. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.075)
    - 75 and 76. Van Nortwick Field Site. Alkali Bee Site. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.076)
    - NE of #77. Garbe Main Site. Gardena Wn Alkali Bee Site. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.077)
    - 78. Garbe Hilltop. Gardena Wn Alkali Bee Sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.078)
    - 78. Garbe Hilltop Site. Emergence cages to check on second generation of alkali bees. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.078a)
    - 81. Garbe House Site. Gardena, Wn alkali bee sites. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.081)
    - 83. Wagoner - Gardena Bee Sites. April 29, 1958. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-04-29 (Box 6, Item 58.083)
    - 85. Ingham N. Hay Stack. Gardena, Wn alkali bee sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.085)
    - 88. Kreggar. Gardena Wash. Alkali bee sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.088)
    - 105. Ball artificial stie. Gardena Wash. Alkali Bee Sites. 9/18/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-09-18 (Box 6, Item 58.105)
    - 107. #1 Southerland. Wilber Southerland. Artificial Bee Site. Gardena. 4/29/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-04-29 (Box 6, Item 58.107)
    - 107. #2. Wilber Southerland, Artificial Bee Site, Gardena. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-04-29 (Box 6, Item 58.107a)
    - 108. Stephenson Artificial. 10/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-10-14 (Box 6, Item 58.108a)
    - 108. Stephenson Artificial. 10/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-10-14 (Box 6, Item 58.108b)
    - 108. Stephenson Artificial. 10/14/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-10-14 (Box 6, Item 58.108c)
    - Gaugl. 1958. Alfalfa Seed. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958 (Box 7, Item 58.200)
    - Kwak #2. Alkali Bee larvae in soil sample. No mouse damage. 3/19/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.201)
    - New Office Bldg. May, 1958. No negatives. 2 prints of different views. 1958-05 (Box 7, Item 58.202)
    - Kwak #4. Mouse Damage on Soil Sample (Bee). 3/19/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.203)
    - Kwak #5. Mouse Damage in Soil Sample (Bee). 3/19/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.204)
    - Kwak #6. Mouse Damage in Soil Sample (Bee). 3/19/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.205)
    - Kwak #7. Mouose Damage in Soil Sample (Bee). 3/19/58. 4x5 neg.; print. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.206)
    - Pictures of Bee and Beefly Larvae in Soil cores. Also Mouse Damage to Bee's at Kwak' Dump Site. 3/19 and 4/3/58. No negatives. 7 prints with labels and dates on backs. 1958-03-19 (Box 7, Item 58.207)